[{"question": "  hi, you guys.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " what&#146;s the matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " well it&#146;s just&#151;it&#146;s one of those situations that i just hate. y&#146;know? a massage client gave me three tickets to the helmet-pelts exhibit at the morgan chase museum.", "answer": "  now you&#146;re thinking you gotta sleep with him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " no! no! it&#146;s just that he gave me three tickets and there are six of us!", "answer": " i&#146;ll give up my ticket.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " me too.", "answer": " okay that&#146;s so generous!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " and i think ross is generous too.", "answer": " great! okay then it&#146;s just us girls! monica and rachel:  great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " so what-what is the exhibit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " it&#146;s mostly just photographs of lesbian love scenes interspersed with video games and free sandwiches.", "answer": " oh man!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey ross listen chandler got you out of going to the lesbian sandwich museum this weekend!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " thanks? but i have plans; elizabeth and i are going out of town.", "answer": " oh that&#146;s great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " i mean think about all the money that you&#146;re gonna make!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " why? what?", "answer": " well, her father pays you for baby-sitting right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " no, no, that&#146;s funny. but maybe it&#146;s time to move on, let it go, y&#146;know? stop it! besides, rachel is going out with elizabeth&#146;s father, so ah, he&#146;s much older than she is. looks like i&#146;m not the only one interested in fossils, huh?", "answer": " i mean ross all that does is remind us that you are interested in fossils.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " ross.", "answer": " oh, come on you guys; that&#146;s funny! y&#146;know? because he&#146;s need&#151;he&#146;s got like a hearing aide y&#146;know, &#145;cause-&#145;cause y&#146;know, &#145;cause he&#146;s all old, and&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " okay look, ross, just so you know that since lizzie likes you so much, i&#146;ve decided to accept the fact that you&#146;re going out with her.", "answer": " really? that okay, that&#146;s great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " yeah. but then i changed my mind. i&#146;m funny like that. so i told lizzie, now i&#146;m telling you, i don&#146;t want you seeing my daughter anymore.", "answer": " all right look, i-i realize it upsets you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " yes it does.", "answer": " but, elizabeth and i are-are both adults and so i don&#146;t think there&#146;s really anything you can do about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " i&#146;ll call the university and tell them about your relationship and have you fired.", "answer": " ohh! a man with a plan!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh, this is so exciting! you get your picture back up on the wall of fame! eek!", "answer": " i know. it was so cool when i was up there before. me and jim belushi would just be crackin&#146; up about something&#133; then i get fired off of days of our lives and he takes me down. now he&#146;s just laughing at me. look at him, that smug belushi bastard, i&#146;ll&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey! so i&#146;m back. the dry cleaner: who are you?", "answer": " joey tribbiani! from the wall!  okay, maybe this will jog your memory, huh?  huh? okay eh-ah-anyway, i&#146;m ready to go back up on the wall i&#146;m the star of a new tv show. the dry cleaner:  show me in the table.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh well, it&#146;s not on tv yet. the dry cleaner: well, then it&#146;s not on the wall yet.", "answer": " okay, fine, i will bring you a tape, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh, i love museums!", "answer": " umm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " soakin&#146; up all the culture.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " where do you want to start?", "answer": " ooh, the gift shop!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " hey, and then lunch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " oh, wait yes, but i can&#146;t eat too much. paul is taking me out to dinner tonight, he said he has a big surprise planned.", "answer": " oh wow. what, do you think maybe he&#146;s gonna tell you that he&#146;s gay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " what?! no! why?!", "answer": " no reason! that would just be a really big surprise, right?  the museum official:  you can put the aisle over here , and put the wedding ceremony right over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " i didn&#146;t know you could get married here.", "answer": " this would be a beautiful place to get married, yeah, but i wouldn&#146;t put the aisle there and i would never have the ceremony there!  i mean you&#146;d have the ceremony under this big beautiful arch.  the museum official:  may i help you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " monica, you should totally put your name down on the list", "answer": " what?! are you crazy?! i&#146;m not getting married! i&#146;m not even engaged.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " yeah hon, it can&#146;t hurt to put your name down! i mean in if two years if you&#146;re not engaged you just don&#146;t use it.", "answer": " well, i mean i guess there is no harm in putting my name down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna do it too!", "answer": " me too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " really? who would, who would you marry?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, i don&#146;t have anyone right now. y&#146;know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " oh pheebs.", "answer": " don&#146;t feel too sorry for me. at least my boyfriend isn&#146;t gay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " phoebe, that stuff is&#133;", "answer": " don&#146;t even get me started on yours!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": "  hey! so, did you watch the tape of my show? the dry cleaner: i did.", "answer": " all right, let&#146;s get me back up there!  the dry cleaner: no! it don&#146;t go up on the wall!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " what&#151;but you saw the show! the dry cleaner: yes, it was very offensive to my people!", "answer": " dry cleaners? the dry cleaner: russians! it showed them as terrorists and villains!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " okay! okay, look! you-you-you got harrison ford up there! the dry cleaner: that&#146;s right. mr. ford is a very good customer, he brings us a lot of clothes; you bring us nothing!", "answer": " okay well that may be true. but, in-in okay, air force one the russians were terrorists! and evil! and plus he kills a bunch of them! that-that-that&#146;s offensive to russians. the dry cleaner: i&#146;ve never seen it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " this place is really beautiful!", "answer": " yeah, i&#146;ve been coming here since i was a kid. this used to be my grandma&#146;s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " wow! the only thing i got from my grandmother was her eyes. i mean not-not her actual eyeballs, but, but people say that my eyes&#151;do-do you want to make out?", "answer": " sure!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " are you okay? what&#146;s wrong?", "answer": " ehh, i was just, i was just thinking about your father.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " well, whatever works for ya&#133;", "answer": " no. no-no uh, he just, he just really freaked me out before.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " oh. well, so we have to hide our relationship from one more person. big deal. besides, it&#146;s kinda fun hiding.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  hey umm, you brought protection right?", "answer": "  why?! are there like bears or something?!  ohh. oh, protection. yeah-no, yeah-no, that-that-that i forgot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " i&#146;ll just run to the store and get some.", "answer": " oh no! hey-hey, i&#146;m the guy! i&#146;ll get it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " do you know where the store is?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " do you want to ride around town on my little pink bicycle?", "answer": " a little bit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  i&#146;ll be back in ten minutes.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " why don&#146;t you get in the hot tub and i&#146;ll meet you there.", "answer": " ohh, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " it&#146;s so secluded up here.", "answer": " i know. i like it up here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " what&#146;s the matter honey? did you see a little mouse?", "answer": " no-no! big bear! big bear outside! i think i-i&#151;would you&#151;actually, would you go check on that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " honey, we don&#146;t have any bears here.", "answer": " well, okay. would-would you get me a diet coke?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " okay.  what?! what are you doing here?!", "answer": " what are you doing here?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " i came with paul!", "answer": " yeah, i recognize the ankles!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " get up!", "answer": "  here you go honey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " ahh. thank you!", "answer": " diet coke.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " op, ice. i need ice.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " i&#146;ll be right back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": "  you and your ice.", "answer": " ugh! get out! get out! go! come on!  no! not in there! he&#146;s in there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  did you really hear a bear?", "answer": " go-go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  here you go honey. one diet coke with ice.", "answer": " ohh, thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " i&#146;m so happy that you&#146;re here.", "answer": "  here i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": "  elizabeth! oh look, elizabeth&#146;s here! who are you talking to?", "answer": " uh, you guys?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " how did you know we were here?", "answer": " umm&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well, she-she ob-obviously saw the tire tracks that were leading up to the closed garage.", "answer": " obviously.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " did-did you come up here to work on that term paper or something?", "answer": " yeah! yep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " well, why do y&#146;know go in that room  and do your homework?", "answer": " ohh, i wouldn&#146;t do it in there. that&#146;s my dad&#146;s bedroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " that&#146;s your, that&#146;s your dad&#146;s bedroom.  that&#146;s your dad&#146;s bedroom!", "answer": " why are you yelling?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hi, honey.", "answer": "  see you later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " what? i-i bought groceries, i was gonna make you dinner!", "answer": "  well next time ask! or at least wait for me to ask!   the museum official:  hi, this is heldi from the morgan chase museum. i&#146;m calling for monica geller.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " oh no! the museum official:  i want to let her know that there was a cancellation and if she&#146;s still interested in having the bing-geller wedding at our facility, it is available&#133;", "answer": " oh please, he didn&#146;t hear it! he didn&#146;t hear it!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " can i help you?", "answer": " uh yeah, where-where&#146;s the guy who decides who&#146;s pictures go up on the wall?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " he&#146;s not here right now.", "answer": " oh, you&#146;re kidding me! all-all right, well make sure you tell him that joey tribbiani stopped by to drop off all of these clothes. okay? i&#146;m an actor; i&#146;m kinda getting my picture up there on the wall.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " so lizzie, are-are-are you planning on staying the night?", "answer": " oh no-no believe me, i&#146;m leaving as soon as possible!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " good. good. not that we don&#146;t want you to stay, obviously you&#146;re welcome&#151;how much more homework do you have?", "answer": " ahh, i just have one problem left that i do not know how to solve. uhh, rachel maybe you want to come upstairs and help me figure it out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " really? okay. okay, i-i&#146;ll go upstairs.  if-if you get me something from the car.", "answer": " what do you need from the car?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " surprise me.", "answer": "  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " phoebe!", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " have you seen chandler?!", "answer": " no! why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " the woman from the museum called and said that there was a cancellation and that we could move up our wedding and chandler heard!  i know! how bad is this?!", "answer": " well for the regular guy, it&#146;s bad, but chandler, oh dear god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " i know! i know! and he totally freaked out and i can&#146;t find him anywhere!", "answer": " what are you gonna do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " well, i&#146;m never gonna listen to you again, that&#146;s for sure!  &quot;y&#146;know, harm can it do if you go and put your name down?&quot;", "answer": " rachel said that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " i didn&#146;t do that! who would&#146;ve done that?! the dry cleaner:  son of a bitch!", "answer": " okay, maybe ask this guy. the dry cleaner: you, get out of my shop!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " well, what did he do? the dry cleaner: he went out with my wife!", "answer": " joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " well, we should go.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " ross? ross?", "answer": " elizabeth!  okay. okay.  i&#146;m gonna go out this window.  i&#146;ll meet you at the front door. just tell them you&#146;re going home, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": "  oh wait-wait-wait!! no! don&#146;t go in there! don&#146;t go in there! i need another soda!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " ross!", "answer": " oh my god ross! what in heaven&#146;s name are you doing here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": "  and that is why we cannot see each other anymore.", "answer": " ross. you and i are going to have to have a little talk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " daddy!", "answer": " you&#146;re next!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " let me just see if i got this straight. i tell you to stay away from my daughter or i&#146;ll have you fired. what you heard was, &quot;take my daughter, come up to my country house, and ruin my weekend with rachel!&quot;", "answer": " okay, please-please paul, just let me explain&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " no, let me explain! fired!!", "answer": " all right, fine! fine! have me fired! but uh, i want you to know that you and i are not all that different. i mean, i too am a neat guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": "  what?", "answer": " and i too am just a love machine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": "  i&#146;m so sorry. please, stop freaking out.", "answer": " i&#146;m not freaking out. why would i be freaking out? a woman named heldi called and said we were getting married, but that happens everyday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " honey, we were at this beautiful place, and i-i-i just put our names down for fun! i mean, what&#146;s the harm in that?", "answer": " right here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " chandler, please don&#146;t think i was trying to pressure you. phoebe and rachel&#133;", "answer": " phoebe and rachel! so the people that knew about our wedding before me were you, phoebe and rachel, heldi, and apparently some band called starlight magic 7 who are available by the way!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " it was a mistake. please don&#146;t take this to mean anything, because it doesn&#146;t.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yes, if it really doesn&#146;t mean anything, because you know that i&#146;m just not ready&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " i know! i know.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  hey, did she buy it?", "answer": " totally.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " so did heldi show you the place?", "answer": " yeah, it&#146;s beautiful.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe you&#146;re gonna ask monica to marry you!", "answer": " i know.  ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " hey gunther.", "answer": " hey! take these cappuccinos to table 11 and that guy over there  wants the biscotti.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " oh uh, well i just came in for a cup of coffee to go.", "answer": " do you still work here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " no! no, i quit a long time ago.  did i forget to you that one? i&#146;m sorry.", "answer": " oh that&#146;s cool, i was gonna fire you anyway.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}]